[{"answer": "Well, actually the president tried to get online and my daughter tried to get online.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Have you tried to get online yourself?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Well, it's not for -- it's not a good result as far as I think something very bad for the American people, Piers.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "How on earth has this happened?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "You know, I think as time goes by, I think more and more people are going to see that fighting over the implementation of a law that would be terrible for the American people is worth it and so this is going to require legislative action and you're going to see Democrats coming to the table because they're going to be shamed into admitting that the President lied and that it's a law that would be a disaster for the American people and a lot of these Democrats want to try to get reelected so they're going to come back to the table.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Does the shambles of what is going on in any way justify shutting down the government?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, I mean either he lied to the American people or is that he's so grossly negligent in doing his job that it's akin to a lie, Piers.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Did he tell the American people repeatedly a bare faced lie in your eyes?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I think the honorable thing to do in a case like this, when you've been given the honor and the privilege to serve as a secretary, a cabinet secretary in the United States for any president, I think there's a certain amount of honor and dignity and saying, \"Look, this is a big mess.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Should Kathleen Sebelius resign or be fired over this, given she's now said that she must to be held person accountable?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I don't know who's going to be the nominee, Piers.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Could you see a position where Ted Cruz is your party's nominee to be president?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I mean, it's all a bunch of nonsense, I mean the fact of the matter is that to the Affordable Care Act is working.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "So let me start with you, Congressman Pallone, what would you make about Reince Priebus said there?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Look, yeah.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "... have to do with insurance policy.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What about telling the truth?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "That's exactly was.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Am I looking at poo and crusted vomit?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Yes here, can you put the glass onto?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I think the first thing you have to do is make sure you're looking at a complete narrative.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "How do we get America back to work?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I don't think things like the skills gap or infrastructure, or currency devaluation, or manufacturing outsourcing.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What is going on with the education system in America that is leading to this kind of statistics?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Good Lord, I'm just going to sip from my champagne.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Would you ever consider plummeting the debts of working in Washington DC?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Retire.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "And if you do, what would you do?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "This came from a zoo.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "So this manure came from where?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, once in awhile you might get an elephant dung.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What sort of animal produced it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Can it be that again?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "We're still the greatest manufacturing force on the planet.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "In with new technology now, the way to do this?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "The but is Walmart has committed to bring back 50 billion jobs and manufacturing in the next 10 years.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What's the but?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "$50 billion worth of manufacture...", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Maybe, but I think a better argument is, you know, well, the show that you work on for instance and many shows that if they're very, very popular, not a crisis and all but it's interesting to see an American Idol for instance or an America's Got Talent.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "You think that's a good argument?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "My kids have to learn about losing as well as winning, it makes the winning sweeter.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Someone is going lose and then they'll feel bad and then what?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a lot of work and it's a crowded market now.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Has it been everything you hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Has it drawn out more racism?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I think it's impossible for me just as an individual to gauge whether it's more or less.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Or has it begun to deal with it properly?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Keep that on a little (inaudible).", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "To the question?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "About 40 years.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "When is the last time Jack did something like this?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "It may one of -- be Johnny Carson.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Was it Carson?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Let's do it on CNN.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "It will, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, I'd love to have Hilary come play any instrument, that would be great, you know.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Let's talk about your dream guest who will it be right now?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "What do you make at Chris Brown?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Well, by the way Mike Tyson just came out and said, \"He's worried about Chris Brown.\"", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Why should I not think terrible things about Chris Brown?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Yeah, because gosh he's such a talented entertainer and you got to think that somewhere in his past there's some kind of pain and I don't think he's a bad kid, I think he's a kid doing bad thing.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for it?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, he's going to have to preach the nine commandments and I think that's going to be a strange, but that was in the (inaudible).", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "And what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Oh I love doing stand-up.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "You still do stand-up?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I call -- well, you know, what I go on Sunday nights with Jay Leno down to a place called Comedy and Magic or because he's there every Sunday and sometimes I go out to the ice house I love to still get on the stage on a Sunday night and get ready for the week, and if I can go out after our show some nights, I'll do it.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "And how could you do it?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Oh, we always talk about doing comedy America, as a matter of fact on the third class of wine you come up with some really great scripts, R. Kelly takes your wife and you have to come find her in Queens.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "What about Eddie Murphy, you obviously was so brilliant together, is there chance, any plan you've spoken about doing something again?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "He is coming on Friday and in the next three weeks I have -- he is bringing Paulina Rubio, and I have everybody from Cal to Murphy, everything in between, every type t-shirt in between, you know.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What are you doing to him?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Anything.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "What a movie?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "You don't followed it?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Who is pound for pound the funniest person you've ever seen in your life?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "A lot of stand-up say that, is he deemed to be the unofficial king?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Well, first of all he wasn't afraid to go places in the world of honesty that some comments (ph) won't go to, like if my mother run a whole house I might not tell you.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "What made him brilliant?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "You're one of my comedic legends.", "docId": "131030pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "You know what?", "qSentId": 672}]